IAMES COPPARD

Software Engineering Student

jamescoppard024@gmail.co	m 👩	nzbasic
	A	Auckland CBD, Auckland
	ABOUT ME	

I am currently studying at the University of Auckland for a Bachelor of Engineering, specializing in Software Engineering. I am passionate about learning new technologies so I have created projects that help the communities that I am apart of to help me learn and to give back.

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF ENGINEERING (HONS)

UNIVERSITY OF AUCKLAND | 2019 - 2022

Specialization: Software Engineering **Software Engineering GPA:** 8.375/9

Experience

QA ENGINEER INTERN

PORTAINER.IO | DEC 2020 - PRESENT

- Testing new features involving the management of Kubernetes clusters and Docker and documenting the tests taken for each PR.
- Performing release and post release tests to ensure smooth releases.
- · Learned to work in an agile environment

TRAVEL CONSULTANT

KIWI EXPERIENCE | DEC 2017 - MARCH 2020

- Customer Service, Sales, Administration, Invoicing, Managing Records
- Role relied heavily on good communication skills and problem solving.

Software Projects

OSUTRACKER

- Website for users to track their progress in the game osu! and also the collective progress of countries.
- MERN stack application with additional NodeJs data collection servers collecting and hosting the data of over 5000 users. It is dockerized and runs on my homeserver.
- · Using atomic, mobile first design to insure the application is responsive
- · Has a public facing API for developers to use, with a dedicated documentation website for convenience.
- · Found on osutracker.com, wiki at wiki.nzbasic.com.

QUINZICAL

- A New Zealand trivia application written in Java utilizing JavaFX.
- · Collaborative project where we worked to meet the clients needs.
- Learned a lot about UI design, OOP design patterns, using GitHub in a team and how to collaborate on a Software project effectively

_			
	h h h h		0
100			
	hno	ıvuı	
		, -	